itsallaboutlinks.com 2010-06-25

# Web Directory - Privacy Policy

tsAllAboutLinks.Com respects and protects your privacy, when you are using our free ItsAllAboutLinks.Com Search and Directory. Information that may specifically identify you as an individual is never collected nor shared with third parties. 

 **ItsAllAboutLinks.Com and Cookies**

Upon your first visit to ItsAllAboutLinks.Com, ItsAllAboutLinks.Com may send a "cookie" to your computer. Cookies are used by many sites, an internet search on 'cookies' may provide you with more information that you will ever need. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. ItsAllAboutLinks.Com will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most internet browser are set up to accept cookie. Although it is possible to reset your computer settings to inform you of cookie or to reject cookies, such actions may interfere with your searches at ItsAllAboutLinks.Com

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

ItsAllAboutLinks.Com does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the site submission process. This information is used to contact you if there is a need for a  revision to your site reviews. ItsAllAboutLinks.Com notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. This information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

 **Links to Other Sites**

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by ItsAllAboutLinks.Com searches are developed by people over whom ItsAllAboutLinks.Com has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns. 

 **ItsAllAboutLinks.Com Shared Information**  

ItsAllAboutLinks.Com may share information about you with advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. This shared information is in the form of compiled data that does not identify individuals.  
For example, we may disclose keyword searches, or the amount of time spent in searching at ItsAllAboutLinks.Com. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

 **Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy  **

By using the ItsAllAboutLinks.Com Search and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy. ItsAllAboutLinks.Com may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be dated and posted on this page. The purpose of this Policy is to make you an informed Internet user - fully aware of what information is collected and the uses for complied information.

 **Additional questions?**  

If you still have questions feel free to [contact us](http://www.itsallaboutlinks.com/contactus.htm).
